Thank you for coming along at short notice to the committee.
Obviously, with the avian bird flu
publicity and
finally hitting our shores after
a number of years, it'd be very
useful for us to get a briefing on what's happening, how
you see it rolling out, and the responses.
So I'll leave it in your hands, Stuart.
Yeah. No, no. Thanks very much. And yeah, thanks for the opportunity.
Obviously, it has arrived in New Zealand,
so good to have this opportunity to talk through a few.
We've got the slides here. We'll just run through those quite quickly.
Just a bit of-
Yep
... what we know about bird flu, where we're at, and what we're
doing,
or what we've done since those two detections.
And then obviously, there'll be questions.
We've got some colleagues here from the Department of Conservation with us as well,
who can talk about wild birds and vaccination,
and other MPI colleagues as well, that we'll be able to cover off what you're
interested in talking about. So I'll hand over to Mary Van Andel, who's our Chief
Veterinary Officer, to just run through those first few slides on avian
influenza and where we're at in the Australian situation,
and then we'll go from there.
Perfect. Thanks very much, Stu. Good morning, everyone.
So highly pathogenic avian influenza, on the first slide
there.
So a disease that has been prevalent in bird populations
around the world for decades and decades.
We've known about it for a very long time.
In the past, it's been something that's been limited to the northern hemisphere,
and it's been seasonal. What happened in 2020 is that a new strain of this
virus emerged somewhere in the northern hemisphere.
This is the one that we're talking about today and the one that we've detected in
New Zealand for the first time in the last two weeks.
That one called clade 2.3.4.4b, and that was
different. Said it before, right?
That strain was different, and the reason it was different was
because it was spreading in a highly pathogenic form with wild
birds. And not with just one or two species of wild birds,
with a vast number of species. Things like shore birds,
marine birds, those kinds of things.
Previously not a species that had carried the disease, but now
yes. So what happened with that was that it moved across the northern hemisphere.
Because of this change in species distribution,
for countries where this had previously been a seasonal thing, that was no longer
the case. Colleagues in the US and the UK told us about
how in
'22, '23, in that season for them in the UK, they
had cases almost year-round in their
poultry. Right? And so
what hasn't changed about the virus is that it's a low risk to human health.
Okay? So that hasn't changed. That's still the same.
Because of the large number of infected birds around the world,
the number of spillover events into mammals that have been tested and
recorded has increased a lot. And so what we have is
in more than 50 species, 60 species of mammals, this being
detected. We have very few instances of mammals passing this
disease between each other. No cases in humans.
We have the example of dairy cattle in the US, which we can talk about further.
We have a whole population of dairy cattle in the northern hemisphere who have
been tested for this disease and not found. Right?
And so the vast majority of countries who have dairy cattle and who have this
disease have no incidence in dairy cattle.
The US had
a very small number of spillover events, but then moved their
cattle and spread the disease very dramatically in their population.
Yes, so it does affect mammals. Things like sea lions and
seals, those are impacted because they eat dead birds.
Okay.
So in Australia, what we have is,
they found their first detections of this strain of disease
before we did, a couple of weeks before.
We're up to, I want to look because it has, yes,
27 confirmed cases now in Australia.
The majority of those are in
single ocean-going sea birds.
But what has overnight been confirmed is that Australia has
detected local spread in
a population of-
Right
... crested terns in South Australia.
So this is the pattern that we expect with this disease, that it will come
from the Southern Ocean with migratory, not migratory sea birds,
with pelagic birds, birds who mostly live in the Southern Ocean
and intermittently come to New Zealand and Australia and other islands in the
Southern Ocean. And so that's what we've seen.
We saw this in the skua in New Zealand on Piha Beach.
We saw it in the multiple detections in
Australia over the last month or so.
What's changed overnight is that that virus has spread
to
localized populations of terns, and Australia has reported that
transmission there.
Mm.
Okay.
Next slide, please.
What do we want to talk about? Oh, yes.
So we all know that the first case was detected on the 15th of
July, a brown skua that was found on Piha Beach acting
unexpectedly, allowing people to approach it, which is quite unusual behavior for
a skua.
That was subsequently submitted to the Wellington Zoo
and screened as part of the wildlife testing program that we have with
hospitals and found to have clade
2.3.4.4b.
The second case was a swamp harrier, a kahu,
not a bird that lives entirely in the Southern Ocean. Right?
And so that was a little unexpected.
No.
No?
Not a bird that lives entirely in the Southern Ocean.
That's, yes.
I'm saying yeah. Sorry.
Oh, we agree. Sorry. Sorry, Stuart. Apologies, Minister.
Being an enthusiastic listener, sorry.
Apologies,
Minister. Okay. So the second case-
found in Carterton, also handed in to a bird rehabilitation
center and subsequently to the veterinary hospital at
Massey University, and tested as part of ongoing surveillance of
wild birds.
No other confirmed cases to date, despite many reports from the public,
despite ongoing surveillance at these wildlife hospitals.
I would say that these wildlife hospitals and this network of surveillance is a
high-value surveillance stream.
There we have clinicians who are trained in birds and who know what to look for,
and they have the ability to sample these animals,
and also, importantly, to keep them separate from other animals in their care,
so that that doesn't accidentally spread.
Right. So no other confirmed cases.
The point of the surveillance at this point is that we're looking for the same
thing that Australia has detected overnight, right?
We're looking for evidence of transmission in New Zealand birds, because
that tells us something about what the risk to
poultry and these types of other things are.
There are limited things that can be done to protect wildlife.
But our colleagues in the Department of Conservation have
taken good actions to do what can
be done for them. But the value of the ongoing surveillance is in
terms of increasing biosecurity measures, both for wildlife populations and for
poultry,
as we learn about how this disease will spread in New Zealand.
It seems very unlikely that this disease will be able to be eradicated from New
Zealand wildlife. That's not what has happened in any other place in the world.
And so we need to focus our efforts on resilience and on
protecting the populations that we're able to,
because we can't predict or know how this disease will behave
here, because it's never been here before, and it's never been in the Southern
Ocean before.
That's okay.
Yep.
Good. Thank you.
So yeah, the other thing I'll just point out, and we can talk more about it,
from a trade point of view, our trade status is not impacted at the
moment.
That would only come into play when we have infections in poultry.
So infections in wild birds does not affect our status in terms of trade
and exports.
Mr. Chair, I wonder if it could be useful process and order of events for
us to ask some questions about the wild birds before we move on to poultry.
No.
Or if-
Should we do the whole thing together?
We'll do the whole thing together.
Right.
But we could start with the... Because obviously it started in the wild birds, so
they'll be the first questions probably anyway.
Yeah.
I'll just pick through really quickly the last few bits in terms of where we've got
to of the detection. So look, for the last few years, yeah,
we have known of this. We've seen and watched this spreading around the
world and moving down South America into Antarctica,
and then of course, recently into Australia.
So we've been watching this and planning and preparing.
We've taken what we call a One Health approach, which is really that alignment
between animal health and human health.
And so, in our context, that's
ourselves, that's MPI for biosecurity with our colleagues in the Department of
Conservation and the health ministry, Ministry of Health and Health New
Zealand.
And the focus that's been agreed, Cabinet agreed in terms of the approach,
recognizing, as we've said, that once this gets here
in wild birds, it will be something that will ultimately become
endemic. It won't be able to be eradicated, and it will be here to stay here.
So our focus really is on being able to reduce the impact on
our threatened species, on the poultry industry,
maintaining supply of poultry meat and eggs,
maintaining our market access for trade as far as we possibly can,
and protecting human health. Noting what Mary has said around generally it's a low
risk, but there is a human health
aspect here as well.
We've got a government industry agreement arrangement that we signed with the
poultry industry last year. It sets out how we will
jointly work on and manage and respond to H5N1 and other
poultry diseases. And we've also been working a lot with
local government, with regional and territorial authorities, regional councils,
territorial authorities to plan and prepare.
So on the next slide, what's happened
since that detection, or the two detections a couple of weeks
ago,
so we have stood up a response structure and response
activities in
relation to those two detections.
We've
carried on with the surveillance programs that Mary has mentioned.
It's really valuable, that surveillance.
We've seen a notable increase in public notifications to our
hotline as well,
which is what we want and which is what we encourage.
Following the detection in Wellington and Wairarapa,
we've done further surveillance
across the area.
So we've checked the coastline
essentially from Castle Point down to Cape Palliser,
for any signs of mass mortalities of birds.
Haven't found anything out of that.
We've checked other significant sites, the likes of Lake Ferry and other
places for signs of mortalities. Also, some of the seal
colonies that are a bit more
important, so Red Rocks here, Cape Palliser.
We've also looked at Kaikoura, the seal colony there.
We've convened a technical advisory group to advise us on wild
birds,
with the Kahu detection, to understand more about
wild birds and behavior and movement, et cetera, of wild birds that can inform
our planning and response going forward.
And we've been doing a lot of work and continue to work closely with the poultry
industry in terms of their readiness and preparedness
to be able to respond. We've reached out to farmers, and we're
continuing to reach out to poultry farmers one-on-one to offer
support with their plans and their preparedness and work
alongside them to help them
with their plans and anything they need to do on the farm.
As
has been said,
the biggest thing for the poultry industry is to protect themselves from being
infected in the first instance, so putting a lot of focus on that.
And we have
quick response teams and capability to be able to swing in and-
For wherever the next part of the country is, we pick up a case or cases
that we can replicate what we've done in the Wairarapa and here off the
back of those two detections. And we continue with
the public messaging, which like I say,
has had really good reach for us,
and we've seen that with the notifications.
We've
got about 1,300 notifications that we've had in the last two weeks coming
through to our hotline, which we appreciate and is really
valuable. So,
with that, I think hopefully that gives you a good overview of where we're at
and
obviously, questions and discussion. Thank you.
Yep. Thank you very much, Stewart.
So we've got a series of questions.
We're going to Suz, and then to Rachel, and then to Steve, and I might slip one
in depending on what their questions are.
Okay. I'll be quick. Well, I've got a couple of questions actually, but you talk
about watching, planning and preparing, and you're supporting farmers in the
industry, and I've just heard from a number of...
I've got some egg producers in my electorate who are
concerned about what's going to happen to them.
So in particular, free range, just to get kind of specific, in particular, free
range egg farmers. If they end up having to lock up their birds, how does it
work
in terms of packaging? How long can they call them free range when they're
not free range? But
if you could just elaborate on how you're communicating with these guys, because I
think they feel there's a big strategy up here, but in terms of
them, and some of them export as well, what the impacts of exporting will be.
Yeah.
Just how you're reassuring those guys.
Yeah. Okay. A few things in there.
So
this is going to be
something that is ultimately going to be here and spread,
and we have to learn to manage and live with it.
We're in the very early
days and very early stages of that. We've had the two detections.
We haven't had anything since then, but we know there will be more.
The exact pathway in terms of how it'll play out
is uncertain.
We don't know how all the different New Zealand bird
species will
react or how they will be impacted and where and how it could spread and
the prevalence and how it may stay in certain parts of the country versus
not.
However, at the moment,
as you know, a number of poultry operators and farmers across the
country have taken that decision to house birds given
the uncertainty. So we've had those two detections.
That is, of course, a business decision to house
chickens. We have worked with the poultry industry around
stickers and messaging for consumers in terms of why birds are being
housed, given the outbreak. We've worked with the Commerce
Commission as well in terms of the arrangements around
free range and the reasons why birds would be being housed.
As we move-
So has that been communicated to all the
egg farmers?
Yep. So we've worked with both industry associations
on that, and they have leaned in heavily on that in terms of
the approach with that. As we move forward, and Mary can talk a
little bit more about this, what we'll likely see with
bird flu and what other countries like the UK have seen,
this comes in waves. So what's happened in the UK
with poultry and free range, so they still have free range.
They still have free range farming.
But there've been periods where the birds get housed when there's a
prevalence of outbreak or infection,
and this will likely boil down to regional level.
So in the UK, that's what's happened.
The birds have been housed for periods, and then when the
prevalence in wildlife and outbreaks
reduces and diminishes, then the birds can go outside again.
And that's
where we will get to. But there's
a bit of a road ahead of us in terms of all of that and how that
will play out.
So after six weeks, if the birds are inside for
precautionary measures, obviously, can I still put them in a box and say they're
free range or do I have to order new packaging?
That
will
depend on the ongoing prevalence and
the status of the infection of the disease
in the region or at whatever level.
So yeah. So let's say at the regional level.
There will come a point, and this is the UK experience, there'll come a point where
after a period of time, whether it's six weeks or a month or a couple of months,
with the data and the surveillance and what we're seeing,
there may be a degree of comfort that
actually it's not prevalent or it's not as prevalent as
it has been in that area,
and then it may be safe for the birds to actually go outside.
So
like I say, again, that's what
we will find as we move into this. But where birds need to be
housed for their protection,
that is a legitimate thing to do to protect birds from being
infected.
I'm not trying to tell you how to do your job, but just from the feedback I've
received from egg producers, I think it would be really helpful to
have a step-by-step process like we did for COVID or like we
have with the fuel crisis.
Yeah.
Once we get a one, two, three, four, what happens at each stage, I think
that would be really helpful for the industry.
Yep. And that is where we'll get to that.
Yes. So we do have that drafted up. One of the things we don't understand for New
Zealand is how this will spread in wild birds, and so we have no
information right now about spread in native birds in New Zealand because there
is none. But that is exactly where we need to get to.
So that's the purpose of our bird tag group.
So learning about, and the purpose of all of this background surveillance is
so that we can get to a point where we can say, "This area or this region is
now green. This one is now amber. This one is now red." And we can
communicate that both to the Commerce Commission and to colleagues in
industry so that they can make decisions based on that.
Yeah.
Thank you.
And communicate it before so that-
Yes.
Thank you very much. That's really helpful.
Rachel.
I have a sub on this, and then I do-
Yep. Yep
... have one that's slightly different.
So,
my understanding just in terms of layer hens is that MPI, this is slightly
related to bird flu, but generally as well, is currently
consulting on changing the,
per square meter
number of hens that are allowed inside.
So, outdoor is currently nine, oh, sorry, seven
per square meter. No, nine per square meter and seven indoors.
Is that currently what it is? And it's been changed, so there would be nine per
square meter indoors, but it's not gonna be temporary, it's actually gonna be
permanent. So, can understand why something could be temporary in
order to be able to house birds inside, but I'm just interested in why
the consultation is looking at it being permanent.
My understanding is it's temporary.
Your understanding is it's temporary?
Yes.
Can you check that with us and just come back?
Because I think the feedback I've had from
people within the animal welfare industry is their understanding is it's permanent,
and that's raised some concern.
All right.
So I'd be really keen to know whether that is definitely temporary.
Because I don't think there's any argument about having some temporary measures in
place to support.
Yeah.
Right.
Yeah. And I've got a-
Your primary
... other primary. My primary is do you have the resources you need to be able to,
to manage all of this? Because obviously you've got
all the communication you're having to do as well, of all the research, all of the
lead agency work, and same for DOC.
There's a huge amount of impact on your resourcing.
Yeah.
Have government given you any extra resourcing that's both for, for MPI and for
DOC, or are you being expected to cover this from within your baselines?
Because it is, it's a huge project, um, and we want to
acknowledge that, and, but just recognizing that it may require more resource.
Yeah. So we do. We do have enough resourcing, and budget to cover
everything we're doing.
We also, so MPI is also... We're a large organization with
a good footprint across the country.
So what we do, and like we do with all our other responses,
we lean in and leverage on our presence of MPI
staff out in the regions and outside of Wellington and in all our offices.
So, that could be fishery offices, forestry staff, our on-farm
support people. So we, we are well-resourced to be able to
respond.
And as this scales up and down, we're able to flex around
it.
And if we,
if we need to surge in more resource,
and operationally, we also have
external field service providers, like we've done in other responses that we-
So government haven't given you any extra funding?
We're funded at the moment for all what we need to do.
Yeah.
Like with all biosecurity response activities and large programs,
if there is a need for additional funding in the forward
program or the activity, then that's
something we work through with ministers and cabinets in terms of funding.
What about for DOC? Because DOC, obviously, we know historically DOC does have
funding
challenges. So just because obviously for DOC there's a lot of
consultation and work with
wildlife sanctuaries, iwi, a lot of community groups that do
work with
wildlife. I know in my own community we've got places like Naturland and the Brock,
and that they've been working closely with DOC.
So recognizing that has a lot of resource.
So just keen to know if DOC is feeling resourced enough to be able to
respond.
Yeah. We are. We're in a very similar situation to MPI.
We've been planning for several years now for this.
It's not a surprise. We have stood up a small
team internally, using existing resources, so similar to
MPI. We're just shifting resource where we need it, and we've got a
big workforce in the regions to be able to draw on.
So at the moment, we have everything we need.
I think we'll keep an eye on that. For the foreseeable future, that's
absolutely fine. And as Stu said, if there comes a point where it's
bigger than we anticipated, then we'll take a look at what we need and ask for
more resource.
Cool.
Steve.
Sort of on that question,
the likes of BirdCare Aotearoa in West Auckland, who do
extraordinary work, formerly Bird Rescue.
Primarily, well, they focus entirely now on native species.
They're constantly dealing with the extraordinary
cohort of endemic seabirds that we have in terms of
the COVID. We've got the highest population of endemic seabirds of any city in the
world. Many of them are rare. Obviously, as you've articulated
to us, what we know from the pattern of this
flu is that it hits wild and native bird populations first.
Sure.
Are you actively resourcing the likes of BirdCare
Aotearoa? I know they've made a request to the minister that they need, they want
extra staffing, and they want to set themselves up so that when we do get cases,
which is probably an inevitability, that those
existing institutions that have been working for decades
in the community to do bird recovery
are fully equipped to deal with it.
Is there funding for those, the likes of those organizations, those
NGOs around the country?
So I think the advice at the moment, is
that we want people to be working through MPI.
So if there are sick and dead birds, we don't
want people picking them up. We want them to be
calling the hotline and letting the MPI surveillance team to manage that.
Sure. I mean, these are not people.
These are like expert-
Sure
... bird rescue organizations who are,
they're doing this day in and day out.
And their exact point is that we don't want the public
applying bizarre methodologies to try and deal with birds.
We want them going to existing institutions.
But if we get a big increase in the number of infected wild birds,
surely we want to be utilizing those existing organizations in the community
Yeah. So as Mary said, what we have had in place
with a network of these wildlife hospital facilities around the
country is that we've had a surveillance program with them for the
last period, which has been incredibly valuable.
It's background surveillance for any sort of illness or disease, and we
pay for and fund for that activity.
As we go forward with this,
that network still will continue to be incredibly
valuable. And I think the questions you're asking as we move
forward into this,
those are all the things we need to work through and consider in terms of how we
maintain a good network of those facilities
across the country that continue to provide that value as
we monitor and track and see how this
virus spreads.
So there could be public money to support them to ramp up their operations.
We're willing to work through in terms of what we currently do with
them, what we need in terms of a national network and distribution, and then
the capability. And I think that's what we need to work through and figure
out.
You might have some more time. I've got another question on the-
Yeah, I've got a couple.
So, when we get to the problem of infections in
poultry populations, layer hens or broiler hens,
there's questions about when you have to do a whole
flock
eradication. Is that something you're envisaging?
You talked about managing it, but
if those things are occurring, one specific question is to do with
the use of nitrogen or
gas.
Yep.
And apparently, we have a requirement that there'd be 2%
oxygen,
but that's not consistent with the DEFRA requirements overseas, and
in fact means that we use more nitrogen than is necessary,
which reduces our efficiency.
And there's a request specifically from SPCA that we
allow a 5% oxygen level,
which allows less use of the nitrogen, which gives us more
resource and
allows a
more efficient dealing with that obvious situation we don't
want to be in, but if we're in it.
And I wonder if there's an opportunity to consider changing the
parameter of the 2% to 5% oxygen.
Yep. Yeah. So I'll get Mary to talk to the nitrogen specifically,
but yes. So on that request, yes, well, of
course, we can look at that and work that through.
The first part of your question in terms of the culling,
so when we talk about managing it,
what we ultimately want to do is protect as far as possible poultry
operations from becoming infected.
Of course. Yep.
So that's the start. But yes, if a poultry farm
or a broiler meat facility does
become infected,
the birds do need to be culled.
Yep.
Most of them will die from the virus.
It's a very high mortality rate. So you're talking 90
to 95 plus percent would die from the virus in any case.
Yep.
So it does need to be, the birds do need to be culled,
and it needs to be fully cleaned out and disinfected so that birds going back in
don't get infected.
Yep.
But yeah. Mary, did you want to comment more on nitrogen?
On
nitrogen, this is not a
documented specification in the code.
It's not?
That it has to be, no. That it has to be a particular percentage.
Okay.
So we will raise it. We'll discuss it with industry and
understand where this specification comes from, but whatever is
the best thing for the animals and for efficiency is of course what we should be
doing.
Yep.
This is not encoded.
And there's a preference for whole house gassing rather than containerized gassing,
apparently from a welfare point of view, and that's what-
Yes
... they've moved to in other jurisdictions. Is that correct?
This is to do with the amount of handling for the animals, right?
Yeah.
So if there are very few, then a container is
appropriate. But if there are many, many, many, then of course disturbing
them the least we can is preferable.
Yeah. Okay. So,
we've got a couple of questions.
All
wild animals that are detected with the
virus,
they'll have to be euthanized as well, won't they?
No.
No?
No. So
wild birds
across the world have avian influenza viruses.
Wild birds across much of the world are now known to have
2.3.4.4b. Some of those wild birds
have been severely impacted in terms of their populations and
their populations have managed to bounce back over a couple of seasons.
So they've developed a resistance.
Yep. Yes. So they can form immunity.
Okay.
So there is no evidence that
euthanizing wildlife helps this problem.
Right.
This is not one of the strategies.
And my second question is around vaccine availability
and
the planned rollout of vaccinations, because currently
it's my understanding that it's DOC staff that are,
with the five or six named species that they're
working on. Are they working with
the vets that work in the likes of sanctuaries, et cetera,
so that those vets will be able to administer the
vaccine if needed without having
DOC staff-
Mm
... having to travel to or whatever?
Yes. So we have been training up
vets in a few places.
One of them is Pukaha Mount Bruce. We now have
people trained there and then also at a couple of the zoos
as well. So we're able to accelerate in that
way the number of vaccinations that we can undertake.
Oh, sorry. It's kind of following on from Steve's question, but
back to the poultry farmers or the egg farmers.
As part of your considerations to support the industry, I just wondered, have you
considered compensation in, say, in the case of a mass culling's required
like we did for Mycoplasma bovis? Or is there any consideration
of that? And also, have you also looked at the economic implications of
this for the New Zealand economy in monetary terms, I
guess, how this could progress and what effect it could
have?
So the approach here,
as we've talked through, the approach
here is that the industry
is going to need to live and manage with this because it'll be a thing.
It'll become an endemic disease, meaning it can't be
eradicated. So we will not be looking to
run what we would normally do with a biosecurity response, where something can be
contained, eradicated, and eliminated, and you get rid of it, and it's not in
New Zealand. This is not that situation.
So what that means is that we won't
be seeking to exercise powers under the Biosecurity Act to
undertake culling and so on,
which means that compensation is not payable.
The other thing here also is that compensation is
payable when we run a response and we exercise those powers
to get rid of something, and compensation is also
only payable for
us directing or undertaking activity under
powers. Compensation isn't payable for the impacts or the
effects of a disease or a virus. So in this case, where you have
90-plus, 95-plus percent mortality,
that would not be compensable in any event because those birds
will die from the virus. So the approach here
is that the industry needs to,
obviously, like I say, protecting from being infected is the first thing.
But going forward with this virus in New Zealand,
that the poultry industry lives with and manages with this
being prevalent in wild populations.
We're obviously doing all the work we're doing with the industry to build that
resilience and that capability and the preparedness, et cetera, and we'll continue
to do that. And this is the approach under the government industry
agreement framework that we have agreed with the poultry industry, that
this is
how collectively we're going to have to manage with this going
forward. So those are the reasons why
compensation under the Biosecurity Act is not something
that
is really going to be a provision.
Okay.
Unless we find circumstances or
situations where we do need to exercise a power, but that's not what we're
anticipating is going to be the way this gets managed going
forward.
Okay, thanks. I'd just reiterate that it sounds like you're talking with the
industry, but I would implore you to make sure that that's trickling down to the
actual individual farmers, because anecdotally, that's what I've heard on the
ground, that they're not aware. And as I said, the step-by-step program will be
fantastic.
We'll follow Chris.
Yeah. Thank you.
Rachel's got the follow-up.
Yeah. No, I just want to clarify. I had clarification.
There's a newsroom story that the changes to the number of
hens is
planned to be permanent, and that is being consulted on by NAWAC.
So I would appreciate MPI coming back with-
We'll clarify that
... information on why looking at it being permanent as opposed to temporary.
Well, thank you very much for coming in today.
Thank you. That was really helpful.
And good luck.
Thank you.
Good luck.
Thank you. Thanks.
And yeah.
We'll probably get you in again at some stage.
Sure.
Keep us up to date.
Thank you very much.
No, thank you.
So they say.